Mobile: +62 852 631 22089 / +62 838 7939 7967

Jakarta, 2014



Dear Mr/Mrs,

Based on information about vacancy in your company, I am pleasure to apply and join with your company.

I am 24 years old, committed to a high standard of professionalism and willingness to learn. I've been graduated from Padjadjaran University majoring Management Communication, Media Concentration. I love traveling and reading. I am quick learner and able to work in a team. I had internship program at PT Pasundan Utama Televisi (STV) Bandung in Program and Production Division. I am Owner and General Manager of "Jatinangor On The Sky" Internet Radio in Jatinangor, West Java. Start from March 2013 I am a Marketing Communication Staff at PT. Oktagon Citra Mandiri. I create marketing communication plan for every month, handle event and company branding activity (social media).

Regards,

Putrasio Berlianda

Mobile: +62 852 631 22089 / +62 838 7939 7967

CURRICULUM VITAE

PERSONAL DATA

Name : Putrasio Berlianda

Sex : Male

Current Address : Jl. Sulaiman No.14E Kemanggisan, Jakarta Barat.

Home Address : Jl. By Pass Raya, Komplek Pemda II no. 76 Gulai Bancah.

Bukittinggi. Sumatra Barat. 26122

Place/Date of Birth : Bukittinggi, August 22nd, 1990

Mobile : +62 852 631 22089 / +62 838 7939 7967

E-mail : putrasio.berlianda@gmail.com

Marital status : Single
Religion : Moslem
Height : 172 cm
Weight : 57 kg

Interest/Hobbies : Reading, Photography & Videography, Traveling, Hiking,

Playing football.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

2008 - 2012 : Bachelor Degree of Media Concentration, Majoring Management

Communication, Padjadjaran University.

 2005 – 2008
 : SMAN 1 Bukittinggi

 2002 – 2005
 : SMPN 6 Bukittinggi

 1996 – 2002
 : SDN 04 Bukittinggi

ORGANIZATIONAL EXPERIENCE

Mar 2014-present : Soekarno Hatta 48 (Soeta48)

Oct 2011-present : "Bukittinggi Muda" (Youth Movement From Bukittinggi)

2011-2012 : Himpunan Mahasiswa Manajemen Komunikasi 2009-2010 : PRAPATAN Production (Theater and Cabaret)

2009-2010 : COSMIC Unpad (Futsal Club)

2008-2009 : Unit Pecinta Budaya Minang (UPBM) Unpad

2007-2008 : SISPALA SMAN 1 Bukittinggi

Mobile: +62 852 631 22089 / +62 838 7939 7967

_Additional Course/Seminar/Workshop

January 2012 : Menulis Kreatif Bersama Raditya Dika

March 2011 : Kompas TV "TV Broadcasting Workshop"

Mei 2010 : Gerakan Berantas Kecurangan Akademik Fikom Unpad

December 2008 : Pendidikan dan Latihan Komunitas Musik Fikom (KMF) Universitas

Padjadjaran

WORK **E**XPERIENCES

March 2013 – present : Marketing Communication Staff at PT.Oktagon Citra Mandiri

March 2nd, 2014 : Seminar "Berkarya Untuk Negeri" as Speaker

December 6th, 2013 : Seminar "Communication Management Majors in Media

Industry" as Speaker

June 22nd 2012 : Seminar "Kreatif Bersama Radio-Mu as Speaker

October 2011- Nov 2013 : General Manager of Jatinangor On The Sky Online Radio
September 2011- present : Public Relation and Web Administrator Staff of Twitter

@bukittinggiku

Nov – Des 2011 : Internship at PT. Pasundan Utama Televisi (STV) Bandung

January 2011 : The Documentary Film "Kuliah Kerja Nyata Mahasiswa Unpad"

as Camera Person and Editor

November 2010 : "Olimpiade Tradisional Unpad" as Photographer

June 2010 : Short Movie "VIEWFINDER" as Producer

June 2010 : Making a Television Program "KUIS INDOKLOPEDIA" as

Camera Person

June 2010 : Making a Television Program " COMPASS" as Unit Production

Manager

Putrasio Berlianda